How many did you eat?
I am eating golgappa for the first time.
How many?   Have you
eaten six?
What?   Have you
eaten 12?
Guys, even mom has given up.  So
Piyush has eaten 19.  Avantia has been defeated.
Guys, right now we're sitting here
in the living room.  Look, there is no one here.
Everyone [nasal sound] is missing
today brother.  Piyush is in his room.  Sahil
is in his room.  Kunali is in his room.
Good morning Kunali.
Good Morning.
How are you?  Didn't you go to school today?   It's
Sunday.   Have a
nice Sunday.  We
Piyush and Sahil are sleeping,
should we wake them up?
You think he will wake up and that too before 3 or 4 o'clock.
Kunalli audience what would you like to say?
What would you like to say to those who say that you feature Piyush and Sahil less on Vogue
?
I would like to say that guys, those people do not even get up.
How do we get them on Vogue?
Guys, if he wakes up at the daily time, he will wake up and
come here.   I will
come only then and only then will I do
something here with my family.  But Kunali
lives here.  Kunal said because of the TV that
yes, he will get to watch TV because
I did the right thing by not installing a TV in the room.
Brother, if I had installed a TV in
Kunal's room, then brother, even Kunal would not have come
here.  He just comes because of this TV.
This is the big one.  That's absolutely right.
If he was in the room, he would not have come.  So
I will not install the TV in the room right now.
Why?  Otherwise what will you do today?   Will do
some challenges today.  A tough challenge today.
Man, people don't like challenges.
Why don't you come?
People are saying make family vlogs like before.
Old Vogue,
yes people are wanting this,
guys, there is nothing left right now, what is not left in Old Vogue, there is nothing
left, you have shown the whole family in Old Vogue,
what is left for us, then
tell me what should we do, then let's do a
tough challenge,
we also enjoy the challenge, some audience
also enjoy it,
so what challenge do you want to do, tell me what to do,
tell me what you have to do, I will make you do it today, I will
tell you what to do,
challenge, then after some time we
can make that family vogue, you know
how
because there will be 12 family members there.
How?  How will it be?
You will also have a child.
So, when you have children, then
create a family blog.  Ok?
Guys, now we eat
avocado toast for breakfast.  Look, Antika ordered this.
Guys, it looks great.  See.  So brother,
today's video is going to be very interesting.
Because today we are going to do
Spicy Pani Puri Eating Challenge with the family.
Look brother, we have so many Golgappa and Pani Puri here.
Total 200
but this time it is not normal golgappa.
Guys, this water is very,
very spicy.
Guys, this is not normal water.  So everyone's condition is going to worsen.  Let's
see
who can eat the most golgappas.  Who strummed the guitar?  I'm already
strumming the guitar.
Guitar
[laughs]
burp burp sorry.
Guitar.
Now he is burping right now, friend.  How
will they eat this?
So our entire family
will eat all the Golgappa one by one.  Let's see
who can eat the maximum number of Golgappa and the one who
eats the maximum number of Golgappa will get
a foreign trip from me.  Wherever he goes,
whoever wants to go can go wherever.   Can go to
Thailand.
Kunal, now you can go to Thailand if you win.
Well
brother, Kunal likes golgappas very much.
Who knows, Kunal might win today and
we will take him to Thailand again.
Start?  No, stop.
No.
Let's start with Kunal.   I am feeling a
little hungry, friend.  I haven't eaten since morning.   Have
n't you eaten since morning?   What else
?  For the desire of golgappa.
Wait then wait wait wait.
Chota, I am feeling very hungry friend.
Start quickly.  I am feeling hungry.
Tell me how many will you eat?   Are.  I will
eat 10-15.   I will be able to
eat only 10-15.
Hey friend, start quickly.  So guys,
finally the whole family is seated and everyone has
got their golgappas.  Everyone has
currently got 12 plates each.  So let's
see who can eat 12 first.  Whoever eats it first will get
12 and then we will add it to it.  Look, there
is still a lot here, guys, look here, all these are made of semolina
flour.  So start eating as soon as I say.
Ok?   Yes.
So look there is Kunal.  Kunal
is ready brother.  Look at this after adding water.
I am also ready.
Everyone is ready.  Let's eat our own Golgappa and see
who will win today, who will go on a foreign
trip,
oh Dada,
what should be
prepared for the first one,
oh brother, Kunal has prepared three or four,
brother, add water and
then say start, let me say start, let's say
three to one start,
oh brother, brother, brother, everyone is eating their
first golgappa and that too with spicy water,
look, this spicy water is being
eaten by grandfather too, grandfather, are
you eating without water?
I will add water to this.
Hey, give water to grandfather.
[sound of throat clearing]
Wait,
what happened?  Mummy's condition is bad.  First I got busy with
Golgappa
here.
Mom's tears came out after eating the first golgappa.
Look, this water is so dangerous, guys.  This
is also dangerous, guys.  How many of these did you eat?
How many did you eat?   Have you
eaten two?
Buddy.
How many did you eat?
So is the third one.
Brother
four.  Everyone will go to the washroom after eating.  Do you know.
Everyone is feeling very hot.
Put it.
Hey
grandma, how many did you eat?   I
ate two.   You
ate two, Amma, how many did you eat?
I am eating only one right now.
Well,
everyone is busy eating their Golgappa.   I do
n't understand whom should I shoot, friend.  Do it to
me.
Look at this.   It became
very spicy.
Hey, there is too much chilli in it.   There
is chilli in it, there
is more chilli in it.
Water, water,
oh my tears have come.
Big mom, I am
not able to hear my chilli.
Drinking water is allowed, isn't it?
Drink water, whatever you do.   Let's
see who will eat more.
Smoke came out of my ears.
Brother, Golgappa party is going on.  There is no dinner today.  This is it
today.   Yes, it will work.
Brother, it got hurt.
How many did you eat?
I am eating golgappa for the first time.
How many?
Ate six.
Brother, what is he doing for Thailand?
Aunty, how many did you eat?   I
ate three.
Three?
Aunty, how many did you eat?
Three.
too much.
Yes.  There is no chilli in all the water, there is
in both of them, my water
seems less
now see tomorrow everyone will meet in the washroom
what did you
eat 12
what 12 you ate, I will give you more
and see the first stop is over outside my
brother sir elder father is eating dangerously here
12 and give me this
another plate is ready
brother I will prepare the plate
what happened here I am
not able to eat friend I am
not able to eat
sit down a lot
how many have you eaten?
Four.  Ate four or five.  Five ate five.
What?  Condition of five is bad.   Look
brother, Piyush has only two left.
Look, Piyush has eaten 10.  Big
dad will win, brother.  Elder father is eating so fast.
Just watch them eat.
I am filling it with potatoes first.   Did
you go to the gym this morning?
I am
eating it with great force.
So many strong golgappas near the gym.
Eat it.
End.  [nasal sound] should I get
more?  Guys mom has also given up.
How many have you eaten?  How many?   Did
you eat six?  There are six left.
Elder mother ate six.  Now brother,
take three from there.
[nasal sound] Bring
me 12 too.
Did you also eat 12?
Oh brother, Avantika can also win.
Even Bade Abba can win.  Sahil
accepted defeat.  Badi Ammi accepted defeat.
How many 10s did you eat?  Will you eat more?   Let
me.
I will bring it.  This makes it
12.   Are you
only eating 12?  You have cheated
[laughs]
Put it in,
mom, why are you cheating,
why are you putting grandfather in it,
brother, elder father is going to eat 24 golgappas,
tell me what are you doing, 24
[laughs]
friend, you also don't eat too much, you know there will be trouble,
yes brother, I will leave it,
yes, you have already eaten 12, and on top of that you are eating, you
know, I am eating something, do
n't eat so much, that aunty also ate 12, so
brother, I feel that elder sister's foreign trip is going to be
confirmed.
I have quit.   Done.
I ate 14, I
ate only 14.
I ate 15.  Well, at least I got that number.
I am going abroad.
Piyush, give me some more and eat it, friend.
Brother Avantika ate more than Piyush.   Please wait,
I have to leave immediately.
And he is eating.  He is eating.  And
he is eating it.  Now they will fight among themselves.  Let's see.   Are you
eating?  Now I will also eat.  Piyush.
[laughter]
How many brothers does he have?  15.  Take my 16.
They had a fight [laughs] brother.  Yellow.
Come on brother, the main competition is going on
between Avantika and Piyush.
Look, you are equal.
How many are there?   We became
equal.
[laughter] Here you go.
Hey friend, don't do it.
Gave the challenge.   You have become
equal.
Now we are equal.   Are you
equal?
How many?
16 16
Look, he has moved ahead.  [laughs]
Yes, I have
passed, Piyush has gone ahead of you, let it be, let it be,
don't eat forcefully, friend, don't
eat, don't
eat forcefully to defeat him, do
n't eat if it is just a problem,
yes you ate 24
[laughs]
I ate golgappas for the first time friend,
hey [nasal sound] water, your
stomach will get upset
[laughs]
yuck friend, will you
eat more guys,
this water is too spicy, too much, too much,
if it wasn't for this, I would have eaten more, I would have eaten 30-30
also,
we are not adding water at all, that's why I am eating,
I am eating one more,
I am eating without water, I ate one more,
now it's 17, friend, don't do it, friend, don't do it, friend, it's a
competition,
eat, eat, eat well,
tomorrow there will be a competition in the washroom as well,
who will [ __ ] more [laughs]
potatoes, potatoes, boondi will come out.
Hey friend, I
ate 14 [laughs] I ate it.
So Piyush has eaten 19 and defeated Avantiya.
And elder father has eaten 24.  Now he is saying that he will
defeat even elder father.
Come on, big dad, then big dad.   Will
defeat you.  Now see, no matter what, he will
defeat me.  So let him eat first,
how many are there?  It's 20 now.  Piyush
's 24th
point became equal.
Look brother, it's equal.
Now go ahead and move ahead.
So today's winner is
Piyush.
How are the shoes?  I have not quit yet.   Then
eat it.
Bring it.
Look brother, more people have come for elder father.
Yes, let him win.  He is a child.
I'm letting you win.  I feel like
eating a couple of them.  [laughs]
Guys, let's end today's challenge here.  The
winner here is Bade Papa.  28
golgappas have been eaten and Piyush has eaten
24 and after that who is the third one?
I
[laughs]
go on, okay, you are.  Kunali has eaten 19
golgappas.  Ok.  19 golgappas.
Why have you eaten 19?
This is his 19th.   I'm done having
kids, friend.  You are fighting with the child.
I'm eating too [laughs].
Hey friend, it's okay.
He is not behind.
Children are coming here to rest.
How many did you eat?
ate 12.
You have 12
Amma
four.
I have now eaten five pieces.  Five six you got
four four four
six
so first second and third Kunali came brother,
look how many marks I got in maths,
20/20 is showing for the first time today
and what is it, I got
20,
when I get less marks then I don't show it, if I
show that then I get scolded, look I got
20 guys,
today I am showing 20/20 for the first time, I don't know if it
came by mistake or not, otherwise it is definitely
absolutely correct, see come on
brother, I have got 20 in maths.  It's a good thing.
Guys, dinner is ready but I do
n't feel like eating it.  You have eaten so many Golgappas, right?
So guys I hope you liked today's vlog.  If you
like it then please like it.  Please subscribe to the channel.
See you
in the next vlog.  Thank you so much for watching.
[music]
Oh